What blocks exactly do you need from Susie?
I know.
So
I don't know.
The cherry blossoms are in bloom.
Well, it's spring.
I don't think I'll be doing any chores.
Let's go see the cherry blossoms.
Really?
You're so energetic.
Well, I'm young.
You're cute.
Do you want it?
I'm going to make it soon.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
I'm going to make it soon.
Yuki, don't lie down.
Close the door.
I can't do this.
I'm so wet.
Come here.
Wait a minute.
I'm so wet.
Don't wear pants until the cherry blossoms are in bloom.
Really?
It's not in bloom yet.
You'll catch a cold.
I'm so tired.
Don't you want to go home?
Don't smoke in the room.
I'm so tired.
Is this yours?
Thank you.
I forgot something.
I'm a little worried about tomorrow's presentation.
Thank you for your hard work.
I chose a draft from the proposal of the AI.
I thought it would be helpful to use old drawings that haven't been digitized.
The drawings of the Yamanogawa resort are very old.
The AI may not need them.
If you say that, the AI will judge that I don't need them.
It won't be judged.
Why? I don't have anything.
Yoshino.
Yes.
Which do you think is a genius, Einstein or Mozart?
You're talking about the same thing.
No, it's a quiz.
Both?
Then, Einstein.
What Einstein discovered may have been achieved if he had not been him, but if he had given the data to the AI and made it learn.
But Mozart created music that only he could make.
So the answer is Mozart.
Yes.
The answer is that Mozart can't listen to music.
Whose words do you think it is?
I don't know.
It's Einstein.
He loved Mozart's music more than anything.
Both are too different.
Certainly, they are not the same.
We humans can create something from nothing.
But the AI can't.
I see.
I feel like I was encouraged.
I wanted to say something good.
Yoshino, do you have time?
Not yet.
Nina, were you trying to find it alone?
Well, I guess.
He pretends to go home early to make everyone go home early.
What a caring person.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Please.
Hello?
Yes, I'm still at work.
I'm still looking for the stickers for tomorrow's presentation.
It's okay.
I think I'll be a little late.
This is it!
Sorry.
I found it.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry to worry you.
Good luck.
Today is different for me and for Yoh.
Why did this happen?
I've heard it somewhere.
When you miss having sex with your husband, it's a lesson.
I'm sorry.
I don't want a child right now.
I just don't want to.
I want to be with Yoh.
Thank you for the food.
You were on the way here.
The night breeze feels good.
It's good.
Beer after a sweat is the best.
I'm sorry.
I don't like AI.
It's a human privilege.
But there are food robots and a taste sensor.
But I can't make food that failed to be a robot.
Failed food?
Only humans can make eggs.
But humans can eat it.
You're right.
Why am I fighting with AI?
Is that a room?
No.
It fell down.
It's a mess.
Is it okay to do it at this time?
You're the wife, right?
I'm late for work.
You're the editor-in-chief of a magazine.
You're cool.
What kind of person is your husband?
He works at a cafe.
He's nice.
Not at all.
He does what he likes.
He's not interested in anything else.
Men are like that.
What are you talking about?
He's famous for his wife's feelings.
He makes lunch boxes for her.
I like cooking.
I'm sorry.
I like cooking, but I don't touch the kitchen knife.
I'm embarrassed to talk about my wife in front of a beautiful couple like you.
Don't say that.
Don't make me talk about you.
I'm worried about you.
I'm sure you have a wife.
I'm sure you don't have a wife.
I have a wife.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm a sexist.
Tell me.
How can I be sexy?
You're laughing.
I'm sorry.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Let's go to a good ramen restaurant.
I'm home.
You're always late.
I was working.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I'm a bit of a commuter.
If I were you, I'd be happy to talk to you again.
Um... I've been giving up a bit, but...
I'm trying to face the fact.
Next time, please listen to my problems.
Um... so... you don't have to meet me.
Is it a nuisance?
Not at all.
That's good. I'm on your side.
What? Side?
Why do I drink the same taste every day?
Because you like it.
If you like your coffee, you have to like the taste and the smell.
You can't drink anything else.
That's true.
The way you pour coffee is perfect.
Think about how to make the other customers sleep.
I wonder if I can finish it early.
This?
Hello!
Do you wanna go for some coffee?
Just wonder train been sucking WILL
trl
He talks and looks funny
I like you.
I'm the one who likes you.
I love you.
Yes.
I wish I could fly.
I'm tired of playing the same game over and over.
Because you keep updating it.
This is the latest version.
Go the opposite way from the editing.
Then, the sound will be better.
I'll try it.
I found a hole.
This way.
Ryo-chan.
It's next Wednesday.
Yes?
I'm early.
You can go home early.
I don't think it's a promise.
You promised me first.
I don't know what's wrong.
I'm tired of playing the same game over and over again.
I'm trapped in a maze.
Yoshino-san.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm almost done.
How's your family?
It's the worst.
Is that so?
I'm trying my best.
Today is the farming agreement.
Yes.
The night breeze is nice tonight.
Shinkansen
neko wa ashimoto de odori watashi sore wo nagamete iru
matsu no yoru wa sude ni kuraku ao mado ni mieru hoshi no hikari chikaku
No one comes
No one knows
I dance alone
I can't dance well
That nostalgic song
I'm a dream dress
You're a limitless smile
Feet in front, knees behind, arms open
Like the wind, like the water, we sing
Forgetting time
I'm a limitless smile
I'm home
Welcome back
What's this?
The most expensive one
It's still in the fridge
I'm home
Welcome back
I'm so happy
Stop it
Do you want another one?
Let's make a snack
I'm home
We tend to forget how happy it is not to be unhappy
Hello, I'm home
How are you?
I'm doing well
I'm glad I made it on time for your birthday
Did you like my pajamas?
I'm home
I want to sleep with my grandchild
Tell your useless son
I didn't mean to make you do it
I wish you'd pick up the phone
I'm fine
You're always coming to me
You don't have to listen to your mother
You're not going to do it?
I'm not saying that
I'm home
It's broken
You're a fool
It's been broken for 5 years
I'm home
I wonder if you've changed
I'm sorry
I'm late
I see
I guess it can't be helped
Do you want a beer?
Or coffee?
I can't sleep
I'm relieved for a moment
I understand
I'm home
I'm sorry
I'm relieved
But I'm not home
I see
I'm home
Here you are
What?
Open it
I found the same one
I bought what I wanted online
You should have sent me a message before buying it
I'm sorry
I'm home
Me too
I'm changed
Thank you
I don't like the key case
I said thank you naturally
even if it was a lie
I need to change
I've been fighting with my boyfriend
I'm sorry
I want to know your true feelings
Can we talk?
I'm sorry
It's late
I have to go
Yo-chan
It's okay
Please
I'll tell you
I don't want to be told
I want to change
You said you wanted a baby
I'm sorry
Wait
I'm upset
Upset?
I've never said that
You just didn't do it
Do you remember the last time we had sex?
It's been 2 years
Did you want to do it that much?
Michi
I'm sorry
Yoshino
How was it today?
What?
I'm sorry
Really?
I threw a cushion at my husband
What?
We'll continue our fight tonight
He's good at running away
I don't know what will happen
Don't push yourself too hard
I'm trying to push myself a little
It's fixed
Thank you
That's good
Please sit down
Can I sit here?
Yes
I'm sorry
Sit down
I'll make you some coffee
Thank you
Welcome back
Do you want to eat now?
I'm starving
Do you need help?
No
I'm starving
Yes
Do you want to connect the remote?
I'll be back soon
Did you get my data?
Can you send it to me?
In 30 minutes?
What's the specific time?
I see
I'll prepare the data
If you want to make the main data, make it full size
If you can't, you can cut the material
Yes
I'll send it to you
I'm sorry
It's my fault
Did you tell Michi?
Yes
I told her that I'll be late tonight
I'm afraid that I can't calm down
I heard that you can fight sometimes
About what?
I thought that I should live as I used to
I'm not married yet
But we're not only married
We work and live together
We're good friends
I think we're good as a couple
Yo-chan
I don't want to be just a lover
I want to feel that you love me
Isn't that important for a couple?
I love you, so I'm not married
Isn't it normal to want to be loved?
Why are you so calm?
I'm not calm
I understand
I'll try
I'm...
I'm an ED
I see
I'm sorry
Yo-chan is cheating
She lied to me
She ran away
I'm going to the party
Aren't you going to go?
I'll take a picture
I'm waiting for you
But I feel better
I want to feel better
Everyone, please
Kanaka, too
Thank you
I drank too much
I'm fine
I'll drink again
Thank you
Are you okay?
I feel better
I see
Can I go?
I'll go
Thank you
Let's go
I'm fine
I'm sorry
Are you sure you feel better?
What?
Do you really think so?
I think so
I feel like I've solved a difficult quiz
I don't have to do anything
I'm stupid when I'm serious
Why do you say that?
I didn't think so
Stop it
Is my story interesting?
I finally realized that I don't have to think about it
Yoshino
I'm sorry
I feel like I'm drunk
You're not drunk, are you?
I'm not satisfied anymore
I'm sure it will end as a woman
Wait
I'm not alone
I'm also a sexist
I'm being rejected
I feel like I'm being killed
I'm drunk
I pulled them
I don't know why
I feel like they came out
but I feel like I did
I see everyone's doing their best, what to watch or not to watch?
You will see.
Mym, we're talking about Tamaki.
All the factura are watching me.
Tamaki is watching lunch!
I don't know what they are.
I remember us both
We'll meet again, we'll meet again
We'll hug each other tight
The night and the night sky
The End
Her tears
seemed like tears that had been in me all along
I was avoided by Nino
I was avoided
Thanks for watching!
This video clip was created at the end of the free part of  cái FOD.