I'm going to make a pork cutlet.
First, I'm going to boil the pork and cut it into oil.
Vegetables rich in minerals and vitamins have the effect of reducing body fat.
Even if you're worried about your body fat, you can eat the pork.
I'm going to make a pork cutlet.
It's always a little late to come home.
And Kaede came home late.
I'm going to sleep on the sofa so I don't wake up.
I'm going to work.
Good morning.
Nina, you're the same as me.
Energy supplement.
I'm this.
It's the same.
I'm not.
I have a lot of things.
Please stop.
I'm a sexist.
I'm drunk.
I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble.
I know.
Please forget it.
I'm sorry.
I felt like the door that no one could open had opened.
I couldn't open the door myself.
I'm going to the hospital.
If I'm forgiven, I'll be able to tell her.
It's 542 yen.
Would you like to put it in your bag?
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
If you say it, it will be true.
I'm finally.
I finally don't have to think about various things.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm drunk.
You're not drinking, are you?
Her tears.
It seemed like tears that had been accumulating in me.
It's not just Yoshida.
I'm a sexist, too.
Isn't she strong?
ED?
I may be.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
It took a long time to buy it with Niña.
I bought it when I was in the army.
It was in a convenience store.
I'm going to the funeral.
It's not good to meet the senior.
I'd like to tell you as soon as possible because it's a big change in the food industry.
I'll look at the design.
I may be back.
I'm sorry.
I was avoided by Niña.
Good morning.
There is no coffee service.
It's a pity.
I'll be back anytime.
I'll be back.
Is coffee free?
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I ate it first.
I'll eat omelet rice today.
Why?
Why did you sleep here?
Because I was late to the funeral.
Today?
Why?
I was going to eat.
The rice is burnt.
Please excuse me.
What's wrong?
Why are you so angry?
I'm angry because I'm not good at it.
Really?
I can't stand it.
You're selfish.
Don't live a comfortable life.
You lied to me that you were a good leader.
You ran away.
You don't want to be with me, do you?
Did I tell you that?
I'm sensitive to such things.
I'm angry because you're always like that.
It's not fair.
I have nowhere to run.
I'm sorry.
You're selfish.
It's not fair.
I know I'm doing something terrible.
But I want you to know this.
I think of you as my family.
Even if it's a family,
it's something I need.
We're a couple.
You're not with another family.
Even if we're in the same family,
it's completely different.
I'm not leaving you.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
But...
But you won't hug me.
Are you still up?
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Do you want something to drink?
No, I'm fine.
Go to bed.
Can I have a beer?
Thank you.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
No, tomorrow.
I'm not done yet.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to work remotely.
I have a meeting.
Go to bed.
Okay.
I'll leave you here.
But I have to go to work tomorrow.
I'll make you some tea.
I'll leave you here.
I'll go to bed in three minutes.
I'm sorry.
But in three minutes?
I'll call you later.
I can't answer the phone.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Good morning.
It's not enough for three minutes.
It's time for the couple.
The last part of the manuscript has NG.
I'll drop the last part and do it again.
I'll leave now.
I'm listening.
I'm sleepy.
I'm lonely.
Niini.
Kitara, I'm sorry.
This document has been processed.
I want to confirm the correctness of the text.
Well, this is...
If you don't understand, it's okay.
Wait a minute.
This is it.
The second part is different.
This part is different.
What's different?
Not there, but below.
Not here, but above the second part is wrong.
It's not number two, but Iroha 2-2.
It's solved.
It's nice.
The back is hard to see.
I'm sorry.
I hope you can see the back a little more.
It seems to be.
I thought the back was the main character, but the back is also the main character.
I think it's good to be a heroine.
I'll have a heroine.
It was good to be a heroine.
I think it's good.
OK.
I'm sorry, editor.
You can't use that way.
I'm going to quit.
Well, next year.
Here you are.
Thank you.
But why?
Don't you think?
Men can work, play, and cheat.
If a woman wants to be successful, she will only work.
When you get married or have children, the company pretends to be kind and tries to turn you into a rich man who has time.
I'm desperate not to get in the way.
Right?
But I don't know the desperate woman.
The fear of being saved if you let your guard down.
The sense of crisis that the accumulated career is taken away in an instant.
Doesn't your husband look like a carefree person?
Sometimes.
So I thought I'd do it my way.
Do you mean independence?
Do you want to be the editor of this company?
Don't you want to be a maid?
No.
I want to do it.
I'm sorry I can't come.
It's enough.
Because no one will come to visit the person next to you.
Don't stop.
And tomorrow.
Come to the end of the month once a month.
I'll be gone for about 10 minutes.
I understand, Mom.
I'm going home.
I'm going home now.
What about your father?
He came without saying anything and went home without saying anything.
He's alive.
He's just like me.
How are you doing?
I guess so.
Look at this.
That's it.
I found it at the store downstairs.
You're right.
Just looking at it makes me feel better.
I'll be happy to go home.
Mom, can I go to the dining room upstairs?
I haven't eaten yet.
Let's go.
I'm told to move my body.
Wait.
Oh, well.
Your father may come soon.
Why don't you go see him?
I have nothing to say.
Really?
Then go back to work.
Before that, can you go to the store and buy it?
I'm going to make tea.
I can't do this.
I don't drink that kind of tea.
You're making tea here?
Here's your wallet.
I don't need it.
I didn't tell my mother my opinion because I was afraid of my father's face.
I thought I was sacrificing myself.
Maybe that's why I was attracted to Kaede, who was a dream job and a self-assertion.
I thought I should support her.
I thought so.
Thank you.
It's a new one.
I'm glad.
I've been looking at Kaede's face for a while.
Makoto.
Kaede, what's up?
I was near the scene.
I was in the right place.
Here you are.
What?
A cardigan.
I thought it would be good for my mother.
I put it on the last special.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Can you come with me?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.