I...)
Honestly.
I dunno...
Fix me.
The secret I turn my back on,
You wanted to get Yoshiho, but she said no.
Oh...
I'm watching the dog.
It's okay.
But I like spending time with Mitch.
Oh, again!
Oh, this is still a hundred yen.
Once you take it off, it's not worth it.
I feel like I'm connected, whether I'm naked or not having sex.
I'm going to get burned.
I can't do my best today.
You don't have to do it now.
Okay, if that's what you want.
That's enough. Do you understand?
I'm not playing!
It's not the time yet.
Hello, have you done it?
Yes.
Can you send me an email? I'll check it out.
When did sex become tiring?
You should look a little more back.
It's work tomorrow, isn't it?
Sleep, sleep.
Sex for me now is...
Are you okay?
...just a process of getting tired.
You don't have to get up.
Didn't you hear me?
Above all, if I have a child now...
When you get back, please prepare the credit and pay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Everything I've built up will be gone.
I might break my dream.
It's not like lovers will always be together.
Even if it's a couple, people are people.
After all, it's someone else.
Even if it's my husband who loves me.
Even if it's my wife who loves me.
Is sex that important?
I'm sorry.
If you pour too much water, it'll rot.
That's not true.
I'm going.
Is there anything you want to eat tonight?
Anything is fine.
I'll make what you like.
It's getting late, so eat first.
Goodbye.
But why all of a sudden?
And at that time...
I couldn't do it until the end.
No, no, no.
What are you thinking?
I've moved on.
Is there anything new in the house?
I put it in the shared folder.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
The phone...
No, it's not a big deal.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering if I could have ramen.
But yesterday...
Nina, the meeting will begin.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
There's a lot in there.
I'll continue.
It's a good reputation.
It's delicious.
It's you.
Something's changed.
The taste?
It's you.
It's time to give me a present.
I'm not the type to give unexpected presents when I don't expect them.
I wonder why.
I want a return.
When I want to back up.
So, did you have something you wanted to back up?
I don't know.
I just went around.
Don't take it.
Only men know what's really on their mind.
I'll ask.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Of course.
One or two.
But friendship between men and women doesn't work.
I'm sure it will.
I'll take my time.
You're still young.
You don't like him as a man.
You don't like him as a person.
That's love.
It's the seed of love.
If it sprouts from the seed, it will even break through concrete.
I wonder if Senpai is okay.
What?
I wonder if he has the strength to swallow unnecessary eyes.
To grow the eyes you really want to cherish.
You always say such a bad thing.
I wonder if you have that strength.
Excuse me.
Can I have a witness?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm Tanemaki.
I'm here to get rid of bad eyes.
Yes.
What do you do when a man gives you a present?
What's wrong?
I want to know what a man really wants.
It's because it's important.
Like a thank you.
I see.
What's wrong?
I was consulted by Yoshino Senpai.
I see.
In short, I was told to curse.
Maybe.
Thank you.
Nina.
Good morning.
Welcome back.
I'm a farmer.
Good.
I'm going to sell one house.
That's hard.
Good morning.
I'm glad you got a present.
I heard from Kitahara.
Your husband gave you a present and you were cursed.
I was cursed?
I was cursed.
But I got a bouquet.
A bouquet?
It's strange.
It's not an anniversary.
It's an expression of love.
It's to make your loved one happy.
I'll accept your words.
And...
As a lesson partner, I'll tell you.
Ah...
Ah?
Ah.
Yes.
I see.
I think I've made a little progress.
A big progress.
Congratulations.
Well...
Is it strange?
No.
Thank you.
When I got the bouquet, I was happy.
I thought I could convey my feelings a little.
That's good.
I was rewarded for my hard work.
I'm sorry.
I talked a lot.
No problem.
Nina, too.
Your wife was happy with the bouquet, right?
Yes.
Very.
That's good.
I'm here.
Bye.
Can't you go?
What?
No.
I'll go to the store.
Ah.
Please.
You should go straight.
Don't look sideways.
That's better.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
I'm in charge of coordination.
I can't sell it.
I can't help it.
It's hard to sell.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I'm in charge of this.
But you think you're the only one who's working hard.
No one will follow you.
I'm sorry.
Perfect.
It looks delicious.
Right?
I'll eat it.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm a little out.
Don't worry about it.
It's the same when you eat it.
No.
I'm going to take a bath.
Eat slowly.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll take a bath.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm sorry.
You did what your grandmother said.
There are times when you want to be alone.
I'm going home.
I'll go with you.
I took a bath.
Are you okay?
Actually, it didn't go well.
Wedding anniversary.
I had a job that day.
I couldn't make it to dinner.
I'm alone in the store.
I'm embarrassed to have a bouquet.
I couldn't give it to you.
I see.
After that, I told my wife how I felt.
But it's like I'm blaming my wife.
Why doesn't it work?
Even if you try so hard.
It won't change forever.
I'm going to be stubborn.
Because of that.
I was clinging.
If you stack your body.
There's love in there.
But I realized it wasn't there.
It's the same.
Yoshino-san is moving forward.
I'm the same.
I thought I'd be satisfied with just sex.
But at that time.
I don't think my husband feels that way.
I knew it.
I just pretended not to notice.
It's like a fool.
You don't have to laugh.
You don't have to be patient in front of me.
It's okay.
I told Yoshino-san every day that I was encouraged.
It's not true.
I am.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I have a place to go.
Where?
In the sea.
What?
Wow!
It's a picture!
No, it's not.
It's you!
I've never seen you before.
You're like a child.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're so honest.
I'm glad, too.
There are many kinds of penguins here.
Cute!
It's cute!
Did you know?
There was a penguin the same height as me in ancient penguins.
That's not cute.
It's cute.
It's too serious.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Wait a minute.
Sit down.
Did you get stung?
No, I'm fine.
It's too deep.
I was worried.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Do fish cry?
They all look happy.
Maybe one fish is crying.
I don't know if it's in the water.
It's okay.
I wonder if Nina is crying all the time.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'll be around here.
Be careful.
Thank you.
I was happy.
When I saw Yoshino at the promenade.
No.
I'm sorry.
Nostalgic.
Kind kiss.
I was with you.
Kissing each other.
It's wrong.
I'm sorry.
I think the first kiss is the turning point.
Let's finish it once.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back.
I'll go to bed.
I want you to have dinner with me tomorrow night.
I don't have to.
I'll go out with my friends.
I'm fine.
I see.
What's for dinner?
I'm sorry.
I only have what I left yesterday.
That's enough.
It's okay.
I'll warm it up myself.
I understand.
I'll go to bed first.
Good night.
It's rotten if you pour too much water.
That's not true.
I'm sick of myself.
I'm sorry.
Are you pooping?
I'm not.
I knew it.
You're reading a manga while you're pooping.
Are you constipated?
What?
Your phone is going to fall.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'm not.
I'll go on your behalf.
You're my boss.
I'm fine.
I can contact you.
You have a fever.
I'm going to bed.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Do you have a prescription?
I'm going to bed.
You go to work.
I'll buy you something to eat.
No, thank you.
I can drink water.
I see.
Why are you being so nice to me?
I'm fine.
Don't be nice to me.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you.
Let's go to Mitsumori-ka.
Yes.
I'll get a taxi.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back.
I'm home.
Good morning.
I just got here and just got home.
I wanted to go home because I had a cold.
So I was called.
I didn't know he was a cold-blooded person.
I'm home.