I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Your wife will be mad.
She won't be mad at me for this.
I'm sorry.
I'll throw it away.
Okay.
Here you are.
Are you done?
I'm sorry. I'll be done soon.
Okay.
She comes here often.
She likes you.
What's that?
Here you are.
Well...
Thank you for the cake.
It's okay.
Call me when you're done.
Well...
Yes?
Do you have time after work?
What?
No, I don't.
Why?
Well...
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I want to tell you about our contact.
Do you like me?
What?
Our balance has never changed since we met.
Is it interesting?
Yes.
You let me meet you without complaining.
You let me take a nap all day.
Our balance has never changed since we met.
Where did you look at the hourglass?
Where?
Up, down, or in the middle.
What?
Is it a quiz again?
There are three hours in the hourglass.
What?
Turn it over.
The lower hourglass is the past.
The middle hourglass is the present.
The lower hourglass is the future.
Where did you look at?
In the middle.
Nina?
I look at the same thing.
The lower hourglass is the past.
The middle hourglass is the present.
The lower hourglass is the future.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I can't meet you.
It's okay.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I just remembered.
How was the hot spring?
It was a hot spring bath.
Was it big?
I saw a star.
A star.
I'll get it.
Thank you.
What about you?
I'm fine.
I'll clean up.
I knew it was no good.
I'm here.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry I didn't reply to your message.
No.
I'm sorry, too.
I was working hard all morning.
I'm sorry.
I'm not ignoring you.
I know you're taking care of your work.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry.
I was tired.
I see.
I'll eat tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
I bought a souvenir.
It's pretty.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
You're early.
I woke up earlier than usual.
You, too?
Me, too.
It's not good to sleep during a meeting.
I agree.
Is that for the morning meeting?
Yes.
I'll help you with your luggage.
No, thank you.
I'll go.
Thank you.
Niina.
Yes?
Is this the data you're using today?
Well...
Yes, it's okay.
Oh, I see.
This is for you.
Oh, it's from the hotel.
Artemis, the goddess of the moon, can shine near Orion.
I bought it for myself.
Niina, here you are.
Thank you.
It's a gift for you.
I was so happy.
Thank you.
Good morning.
I'll bring the extension cord.
At that time...
Why?
I know the meaning of tears.
I don't want to lose her.
I know.
I'll go with someone.
I was sold to a friend.
Why don't you go with Ryusei's girlfriend?
I can't.
Didn't you see Ryusei?
I saw him with Kami.
He came back from his parents' house.
He's married.
I didn't mean to show you the stars.
I was so excited.
I ran away from him.
What about her?
This is her.
I did it.
Look.
It's a star.
It's going to be a star.
It's cruel.
Why do men cheat on their wives?
They go back to their wives.
Why?
I thought we would be together.
What?
My wife noticed.
But she said she would break up with me.
She's pregnant.
I can't continue this relationship.
You're late.
Are you on a business trip?
You're early.
I finished the puzzle.
Sit down.
Thank you.
I'll have a cup of coffee.
It's 600 yen.
Two, please.
How about the chocolate ice cream?
I'll have a cup of coffee.
I gave you a bite.
Thank you.
I'm happy to be at work.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
Is this your lunch?
No, I'm not hungry.
What do you recommend?
The most popular is octopus rice.
If you want to eat a lot, roast beef.
I also recommend spicy Gapao rice.
By the way, I and my senior are Gapao rice.
I'm Rupeken.
Why did you get up early today?
I got up early this morning.
I was preparing for the meeting room.
Did you do it alone?
I did it alone.
I need someone's help.
Here are two Gapao rice.
Thank you.
Let's eat here.
I'll get a seat.
Is this a good place?
Yes.
I'm hungry.
I'm happy.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Makoto?
What are you doing?
I was going to go to Makoto's company.
Nina's...
She is a colleague of mine.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm Nina's wife.
My husband always takes care of me.
I'm Kitahara.
I'm Yoshino.
You are the editor-in-chief of Jinja, right?
I'm a big fan of your magazine.
Thank you.
I read your article last month.
It was great.
Thank you.
What did you do today?
Makoto, you forgot this.
I'm sorry.
Did you buy a comment?
I have a meeting with the director of Yamada.
I have to finish it in 30 minutes.
I have to go.
Thank you.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Why are you so busy?
I have to go to a meeting.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I think I have a cold.
Senpai, you are dating Nina, right?
You two are so serious.
Hana-chan, why?
Because you and Nina are in love.
You will be found out someday.
Please be careful.
I told you before.
You have to be prepared for a love that you can't find.
You have to realize that you and Nina's wife will hurt others.
You have to decide what to do.
You should stop being upset.
You will be in trouble.
I will support you.
But you are worried about Nina.
I'm fine.
I lost to you.
I will talk to the manager.
Please come back when you can.
Nina, it's time.
I will go downstairs.
Hana-chan is right.
I'm not a beautiful woman.
Do you want this?
I don't like this.
Is there anyone you want to go with?
You don't understand people.
I don't understand people.
I'm Nina's wife.
I'm always taking care of you.
I don't know what to do.
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling well.
I'm going to rest.
What about dinner?
I haven't made it.
I ate it.
I will buy it if I want it.
I don't understand people.
I'm not sure if I can meet Nina.
I ate it.
It was delicious.
Why did you come suddenly?
I came to the exhibition.
You don't usually do that.
Was it a nuisance?
No.
But if you could contact me.
I was thinking of contacting you when I got to the company.
I don't have a lunch box.
Makoto.
You have something.
You have something you're thinking about.
If you have something, say it.
I'll tell you.
Why are you with me?
What?
It's not sudden.
I know what you're thinking about.
So I'm helping you.
But I can't see your feelings for me.
I'm doing this because I have you.
I'm grateful.
I'm doing this for the exhibition.
No.
Why do you refuse to have sex?
I said it before, but not now.
It's not the time.
When is the time?
One year later?
Two years later?
After I become editor-in-chief?
I'll wait forever?
We can't even have a good time together.
Makoto.
Do you hate me?
Don't you like me?
I don't know.
I've never seen your face.
I didn't think Makoto was so depressed.
I didn't know he was so worried.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to send the data.
I'll send it to you.
Don't worry.
Think about the priority.
First, contact the designer and ask if he can wait until tomorrow.
Yes.
In this case, you should deal with the task in front of you.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Contact the editor.
I'll send the email to the editor.
I've always overcome it like this.
From what I can do in front of me.
The designer is fine.
Yes.
Yokoi.
I'll be participating in the meeting from this evening.
What?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by people who don't understand people's feelings?
Please forget it.
Tell me.
I may have been born a light woman.
At least I don't sleep with people who don't have any feelings.
Welcome.
One person.
Please prepare the basic design.
Yes, I have set it.
Thank you.
Welcome.
I'm sorry, Miss.
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything.
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the confetti yesterday.
I was happy.
No.
I can't eat it because it's a waste.
I'm sorry.
I finally talked to you.
Well.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I want to see Orion.
Miss Yoshino.
Yes.
I'm right next to Artemis.
Whatever happens.
Yes.
I wonder if the day will come when I can touch this cold hand.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
I.
I've been hurting you.
I've been protecting myself.
I'm sorry.
Please raise your head.
I've said too much.
But I'm glad I got through.
Yes.
Let's end this story.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sure I'm unknown.
I've been hurting you like this.
I really have to apologize.
It's okay.
I wonder if I'm going to hurt you like this.
Oh, sister.
What?
Hello.
It's been a long time.
Yes.
Oh, wait a minute.
My sister is coming to Tokyo.
So?
Can you take care of the children?
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I'm fine with taking care of the children.
You don't like it, do you?
I refuse.
About a day.
Is that okay?
Yes, I'll take care of it.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
No, no, no.
Welcome back.
What's wrong?
I thought I'd eat with you.
But I'm not going to leave you.
I burned it.
I think the fire is through.
Hamburg is surprisingly difficult.
I always ate normally.
Kaede.
You don't have to force it.
It seems that the laundry is over.
Kaede will do his best.
What is it now?
I'm angry.
Makoto.
You didn't even let me see you.
What is this?
This?
This is a pancake mix.
Suzuki, do you like pancakes?
I love it.
I want to do it.
Do it.
I'm going to do it.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I lost.
No, no, no.
Don't do that.
No.
Let's play a game.
I'll wash my hands.
No.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Do you want to make a new page?
Yes.
This is fine.
What should I do?
Sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mom.
Did you two have a good time?
Yes.
Thank you for taking care of the children.
No problem.
It was fun.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, too.
Don't be sad.
I'll buy you a drink.
Let's go to the vending machine.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I'm running.
You saved me today.
Thank you.
You're having a hard time every day.
I'm afraid I'll have a harder time.
I'm getting a divorce.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to talk to the lawyer today.
You should take good care of Michi.
She's gotten a lot better since she started dating you.
She's gotten a lot better.
But even if you're married, if you're too fat, it hurts.
I'm fine.
Even if you think you know each other, you don't know each other.
If you want to be together, you have to think about it.
I'm tired.
I'm fine.
I'm a little tired.
A little?
You're mean.
But it was fun.
I'm not a good person.
I may be hurting Michi.
I don't want to hurt her.
Why are you saying that?
I'm trying to be nice to her.
What do you mean?
I'm thinking about it.
It's warm.
I'm going to go.
Are you done?
I'm sorry.
The past, the present, the future.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I found a good place.
Can we go tonight?
I'm sorry.
I can't see you anymore.
I knew it.
Let's go back to being just colleagues.
I'm sorry.
But I...
Our relationship will never last.
It's like a clock.
It's a moment when it glitters.
In that moment,
we're just running away.
I'm sure Nina and I can only see now.
The reason why it's hard to be with you now
is because you and I have a past and a future.
I'm sorry.
Can we talk again?
I'm always fine.
I want you to tell me the truth.
I betrayed you.