I want to see Orion.
It's a planetarium, but I found a really good place.
Let's go back to being just colleagues.
I don't want to be alone.
I want to be with you.
Let's go back to being just colleagues.
Why?
I...
I ran away from Nina.
I didn't think about the problem with my husband.
I can forget him in a moment.
I'm sorry.
But I...
Wait, wait, wait.
Welcome back.
What happened?
I just finished.
It's okay. I'll do it.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
I'm not sure.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
That's good.
It's good.
You like it, right?
That's good.
I want a peaceful life.
I don't want to go on an adventure.
I'll try to do it.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Dumplings?
Yes.
I should have stopped.
What?
I made too much.
It's not over yet.
I can't help it.
You-chan?
It's faster if we do it together.
Did you wash your hands?
It's okay if I burn my hands.
It's okay.
What's that?
What's this?
I can't help it.
What's the problem?
I'm going to turn off the light.
Don't rush now.
Believe in what I say.
It's okay.
We are a couple who swore to be together forever.
I'm going to turn off the light.
Did you break up?
Yes.
I'm not prepared for that.
Can I have a fried chicken?
I'll tell you if you want me to say something.
You're right to break up.
It was hard to break up.
Is that really okay?
I thought you wanted me to say something.
I'll have a croquette instead.
I don't want a child.
I just wanted to make it a little longer.
Do you hate me?
I don't know.
It's so hard to be rejected by your husband.
I'm not reflected in the eyes of my husband.
I'm going to have a meeting with the press.
I'm going to talk to the head of the department.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm going to talk to the head of the department.
Mr. Niino.
Do you want to use it next?
Yes, I'll help you.
Thank you.
Did you have a meeting with the sales department today?
It was decided suddenly.
I see.
I thought there was something else to do in the conference room.
I forgot to get an employee from the head of the department.
I'll ask you later.
You're back to your colleagues, right?
I'll take this with me.
I'm sorry.
I can't talk to you again.
I've decided.
I'm going to talk to my husband.
I'm sorry.
I want someone to tell me.
I can't forget it.
I'm sorry.
What do you want to eat tonight?
I don't mind.
The night is coming.
Which do you want?
I'm not sure.
You're a game.
I'm not good at sheep.
What?
It's rare.
I'd like a blend, please.
I'm sorry.
I can get into the store right away.
Okay.
I'll contact my mother.
You can show her.
Okay.
Good evening.
Oh, Miki!
I've been waiting for you.
What's up?
I thought we could go home together.
I didn't have a reply, so I came.
I just noticed.
Oh, it's your first time?
Yes.
Mishima, she's my daughter.
Hello, I'm Michi.
My husband always takes care of me.
Hello.
Did something happen?
No.
Is the store already closed?
Tonight, we're going to...
Oh, I see.
Oh!
How about you, Michi?
You're going to welcome Mishima.
Oh, no, no.
I'm going home.
Let's have a long drink.
Welcome!
Mishima!
Cheers!
I'm sorry.
I remember!
You took me to eat yakiniku before.
You and your wife.
We went to eat yakiniku.
Oh, that?
When we went to order the wedding speech.
How long ago was that?
Five years.
It's been five years since you got married.
Yes.
How about you, Mishima?
I'm not married yet.
Good women don't get married.
Oh, you mean good women don't get married?
No, I mean...
Help me.
Hey!
Nice!
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
It's not okay.
I'm the one who's crying.
I'm sorry.
I think I'm going to lose.
Look at this.
It's kuppa and cold noodles.
Let's finish this.
Yes.
Thank you.
How about you, Kona?
I'm okay.
Eat whatever you want.
Then, I'll listen to you.
Let's order one each.
Let's share.
I'm not sharing.
I heard from my sister.
What do you eat for the end of a barbeque?
What's that?
Excuse me.
I'm back.
It's a psychological test.
You can tell what you're cheating on.
The one who cheats the most gets...
What did I say?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
What about you?
Me neither.
I'll take this.
Okay.
See you later.
No one's ordering?
My wife always orders carbs.
And...
The one who cheats...
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm too energetic.
I was so annoyed when I took the Parisian,
but we're close.
I guess.
But a couple is...
It's like we're holding something in our stomachs.
I hear that it's happier to be cheated on than to be told the truth.
What do you think?
I think it's easier to be cheated on than to be told the truth.
What about you?
I want to be told the truth.
I see.
Mishima is type B, and you're type AB.
I'm type O.
I'm type A.
I'm type O too.
Really?
We're the same.
It's portrait time.
They're saying I am, anger left out.
They have it like that.
The menus gives me lots of hunger.
Such as?
Me too.
Then let's change it to dessert.
For mystery testing.
Dress up?
Excuse me.
Hello?
What?
No, no, no. Wait a minute. What do you mean?
I haven't met Mr. Iwai.
I'm serious.
How can you lie about that?
Yui, you'll fall.
You'll fall.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I even attended your welcome party.
It was fun.
Yeah.
Yui.
Yeah?
I was happy the other day.
You said you'd think about it.
Yeah.
You can trust me, right?
No, no, no.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
Help me.
Did you hurt your leg?
Are you okay?
You finally looked at me.
What?
I'm sorry. I'll clean up and make dinner.
I'm going to make beef stroganoff.
You like it, don't you?
Wait.
You should leave it like this.
I'll make dinner.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
It hurts.
It's okay.
You can still get it back, right?
A request for a transfer?
I want to move to a place where I can spend more time.
But you wanted to be an editor, right?
That's right.
I told my boyfriend I wanted to wait until I was an editor.
But I'm getting busier and busier.
I can't keep him waiting any longer.
I see.
But that's life.
Is that really okay?
You've been working so hard.
Why don't you try it until you can plan it yourself?
I'm afraid I'll be lazy even if I make a break.
Break? It's only been three years.
Lazy.
When I became chief, when I became deputy editor-in-chief,
I got greedy again.
I've been doing that for a long time.
But Makoto has been alone for a long time.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Let's go.
I'm going.
No, no, no.
What's this?
I found it at the station on my way home.
It's a nice spa.
Well...
Let's go.
No?
No, I don't think so.
If you take a day off on Saturday afternoon,
I'll give you a night off on Sunday.
Well, if it's a day off, it's okay.
Okay.
Really?
I'll ask the owner.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I haven't been traveling at all lately.
I'm thinking about changing my mood.
Sometimes it's good to relax in a nice place, right?
Yeah.
I want to fill my heart with Yochan.
Change of mood.
Relax.
It looks delicious.
It's amazing.
I'll go to bed first.
Good night.
I'm going to bed.
If I can't do it again...
Are you going on a trip?
Yeah.
I happened to be on a cancel this week.
Then, from tomorrow.
Well, from noon.
You don't have to say anything.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your hard work.
I think I should stop curry.
It may break your stomach with high heart rate.
You're going on a trip tomorrow, right?
That's good.
I'm going on a love trip with my husband.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to eat the yakisoba I made recently.
Hana-chan.
You're angry, aren't you?
Thank you.
What?
I'm not going to curry.
Right?
I have to wish for her happiness.
I have to wish for it.
I'm Nina, from Futaba Construction.
I received an email.
I'd like to hear about the withdrawal.
Are you motivated?
It's time to decide the next editor-in-chief.
I thought I'd recommend it if I was serious.
That's right.
What's wrong?
I haven't been looking good lately.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I was falling.
What's wrong?
I don't want to talk about it.
I was sued.
What?
I was the boss.
I knew I was in love.
I didn't get along with my wife.
Why did I get fooled by such a definite complaint?
I was so attracted to it that I could be fooled.
But you broke up, didn't you?
Yes, three years ago.
I got a call from Nina.
I'm kidding.
I want to see her.
What about his wife?
I think she misunderstood that we were still in a relationship.
Then explain it to me.
It's useless.
I'm telling the truth.
I'm the worst woman who takes other people's things.
I'll talk to the owner.
Maybe he knows a lawyer.
Thank you.
But don't bother the store.
I don't think so.
I think she's a good woman.
I'm not sure if I can say that.
The bus is about to leave.
I want to see her.
I'm sorry.
I can't live without her.
You're a good man.
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
I once betrayed Michi.
I'm sorry.